http://www.tntsb.com/policy/policy.php?q=terms

Terms and Conditions
The Name Technology Sdn Bhd ("tntsb") maintains www.tntsb.com and its related sites (collectively the "tntsb site") for your personal information, entertainment, and enjoyment. Please feel free to browse, download from, talk back to, and otherwise use the site. At the same time, please remember that your access to the tntsb site is subject to the following rules (the "Rules") as well as all applicable laws. By accessing and using the tntsb site, you accept and agree to the Rules without limitation or qualification, and acknowledge that any other agreements you may have with tntsb are superseded by the Rules, to the extent any conflict exists.
tntsb may at any time revise these Rules by updating this posting. You are bound by such revisions and should therefore visit this page to review the current Rules from time to time.
tntsb reserves the right, without notice and for any reason, to remove any content on this site, and to deny access of any user or users to all or any part of this site.
Use of the Site
Unless otherwise specifically indicated, you may download material displayed on the tntsb site for personal, non-commercial use only and you may not distribute, modify, transmit, use, or reuse any of the contents of the tntsb site for any public or commercial purpose without the written consent of tntsb or any third party tntsb deems necessary. You must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices on downloaded and/or copied material. Any copy of material from the tntsb site you make and distribute for any purpose must also include these Rules. You may not access or use the tntsb site in any way that could or is intended to damage or impair the tntsb site, or any server or network underlying the tntsb site, or interfere with anyone else's use and enjoyment of the tntsb site.
Copyrights, and Other Rights
You should assume that everything on the tntsb site is copyrighted unless otherwise noted and that it must not be used except as provided in the Rules or with the express written consent of tntsb or any third party tntsb deems necessary. TNTSB NEITHER WARRANTS OR REPRESENTS THAT YOUR USE OF THE MATERIAL DISPLAYED ON THE VISA SITE WILL NOT INFRINGE RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES. Any product, service, program, or technology described on the tntsb site may be the subject of other intellectual property rights (including but not limited to copyright, trademark, or patent rights) owned by tntsb. Any such right that is not expressly licensed herein is reserved by tntsb.
Images of people or places displayed on the tntsb site are either the property of, or used with permission by, tntsb. Use of these images by you or other third parties is prohibited unless expressly permitted in the Rules or elsewhere on the tntsb site. Any unauthorized use of these images may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and other applicable regulations and statutes.
Any product, service, program or technology described in any document published by tntsb on this site may be the subject of other intellectual property rights owned by tntsb. Any such right that is not expressly licensed hereunder is reserved by tntsb.
Trademarks
Among the trademarks and service marks owned by The Name Technology Sdn Bhd are tntsb, Dewan Eja Pro, Kamus
Pro, LiveTranslate and the respective logos of all the sites. All other trademarks and trade names are the property of their respective owners.
Nothing contained on the tntsb site should be construed as granting by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on the tntsb site without the written permission of tntsb or such third party that may own the Trademark. Misuse of any Trademarks, or any other content, displayed on the tntsb site is prohibited. tntsb aggressively enforces its intellectual property rights, including via civil and criminal proceedings.
Submissions
Apart from your personal information (which is addressed in the Privacy Policy), any communication or material you send to the tntsb site, electronically or otherwise, including but not limited to data, questions, comments, suggestions, or submissions is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you send to the tntsb site may be used by tntsb for any purpose including but not limited to modification, reproduction, transmission, disclosure, publication, broadcast, and posting. By submitting material to tntsb.com, you irrevocably transfer and assign to tntsb, and forever waive and agree never to assert, any copyrights, "moral" rights, rights of publicity or to privacy, or other intellectual-property or proprietary rights that you may have in such material. tntsb is free to use, without obligation of any kind, any ideas, concepts, techniques, or know-how contained in any communication you send to the tntsb site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services.
By using this site, you may submit, or tntsb may gather, certain limited information about you and your usage of the site. Subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy, tntsb is free to use such information for any purpose it deems appropriate.
No Warranties and Limitation of Liability
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW, TNTSB DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THERE IS NO WARRANTY THAT ANY INFORMATION OR SERVICE PROVIDED OR REFERENCED BY THIS SITE IS EITHER ACCURATE, THAT SUCH INFORMATION OR SERVICE WILL FULFILL ANY OF YOUR PARTICULAR PURPOSES OR NEEDS, OR THAT SUCH INFORMATION OR SERVICE DOES NOT INFRINGE ON ANY THIRD PARTY RIGHTS. EXCEPT FOR ANY EXPRESS WARRANTIES STATED ON THIS SITE, IF ANY, THE INFORMATION AND SERVICES PROVIDED OR REFERENCED ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS," "AS AVAILABLE," AND WITH ALL FAULTS, AND THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO SATISFACTORY QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, ACCURACY AND EFFORT IS WITH THE USER.
SO WHILE TNTSB MAY USE REASONABLE EFFORTS TO INCLUDE ACCURATE AND UP-TO-DATE INFORMATION ON THE TNTSB SITE, TNTSB MAKES NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS AS TO ITS ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, OR COMPLETENESS. TNTSB MAY PERIODICALLY ADD, CHANGE, OR IMPROVE ANY OF THE INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, SERVICES, PROGRAMS, AND TECHNOLOGY DESCRIBED ON THE TNTSB SITE WITHOUT NOTICE. TNTSB ASSUMES NO LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENT OF THE TNTSB SITE.
IN FACT, YOUR USE OF THE TNTSB SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT ALLOWED BY LAW, NEITHER TNTSB NOR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, OR DELIVERING THE TNTSB SITE IS LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, HOWEVER CAUSED, ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR RELIANCE ON THE TNTSB SITE, EVEN IF TNTSB HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. FOR EXAMPLE, TNTSB ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR, AND WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO OR ANY VIRUSES WHICH MAY AFFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR OTHER PROPERTY ON ACCOUNT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR DOWNLOADING FROM, THE TNTSB SITE. PLEASE NOTE THAT SOME JURISDICTIONS MAY RESTRICT OR DISALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Other Agreements
Your use of the tntsb site, or certain features or information provided through the tntsb site, may be subject to additional agreements apart from the Rules.
Links
tntsb has not reviewed all of the sites which are linked to or from the tntsb site, and the fact of such links does not indicate any approval or endorsement of any material contained on any linked site. tntsb is not responsible for the contents of any site linked to or from the tntsb site; and your connection to any such linked site is at your own risk.
Legal Information
The Rules will be governed by and construed under the laws of the Malaysia Governments, excluding only its conflict of law provisions. Each party to the tntsb site Rules hereby submits to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts within the Malaysia Government, and waives any jurisdictional, venue, or inconvenient forum objections to such courts.
Any failure by tntsb to enforce any of its rights under the Rules or applicable laws shall not constitute a waiver of such right. If any provision of the Rules is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, you, tntsb, and the court shall endeavour to give effect to the intent reflected in that provision, and the remaining Rules provisions shall retain their full force and effect.
You agree to follow any applicable laws in your use of the tntsb site. Among other things, Malaysia and foreign export control laws regulate the export and re-export of technology originating in the Malaysia and such foreign countries. You will abide by these laws and regulations as applicable and will not transfer, directly or indirectly, by electronic transmission or otherwise, any content or software from the tntsb site to or from any countries or foreign nationals in violation of such laws or regulations.
Please also read over the tntsb site Privacy Policy, which are part of the Rules and which you accept. If you have any questions, comments, or complaints about tntsb.com, please feel free to email us at : support@tntsb.com.
©
The Name Technology Sdn. Bhd. | All Right Reserved
4800-2-6 CBD Perdana, Jalan Perdana Off Persiaran Multimedia,
63000 Cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia.
